如今的人痴迷一切闪亮新鲜的事物
People today are obsessed with anything shiny and new.
但那都是幻觉
But it's all an illusion.
一切新潮的东西都会淡去
Everything new fades.
但一座被人遗忘的旅馆还是有些用处的
But forgotten hotels are still good for some things.
毒品交易
Drug deals.
老牛嫩草的婚外恋
May-December indiscretions.
还有一了百了
And ending it all.
我在哪都认得出那副表情
I knew that look anywhere.
见过太多次了
Seen it many times.
这两位幸运的人很满足
These two lucky birds are content.
甚至很平静
At peace, even.
他们说这是他们的结婚纪念日
It's their wedding anniversary, they tell me.
60年了
60 years.
四个孩子
Four kids.
九个孙辈
Nine grandchildren.
他们这辈子过得不错
They've had a good run together.
但她不像以往了
But she's not quite the same anymore
因为癌症扩散了
since the cancer spread.
他无法想象失去她的生活
And he can't imagine his life without her.
她最不希望的就是成为累赘
The last thing she wants is to be a burden.
于是他们来这儿
So they come here...
好独处
to be alone.
好再不必感到孤单了
So they never have to be alone again.
我
I...
嫉妒他们
envy them.
你见过比这更美丽的场面吗
Have you ever seen anything more beautiful?
我只能看到要洗洗刷刷八小时
All I can see is eight hours of hard scrubbing
才能把墙上的血都洗掉
gonna take to get the blood off these walls.
他们为什么就不能在自己家里
Why don't people have the courtesy
爆头呢
to blow their brains out at their own home?
如果被他们的孩子看到呢
What if one of the kids found them like this?
我不明白这为什么非要成为我的麻烦
Well, I don't see why that has to be my problem.
看看他们
Look at them.
你哭什么
Why are you crying?
他们很幸福啊
They were happy.
我觉得我再也开心不起来了
I feel like I'll never be happy again.
我假装我可以生活在没有特里斯坦的世界里
I pretend that I'm okay living in a world without Tristan,
但
but it's...
真的很艰难
it's been difficult.
而且
Besides,
就对女伯爵的了解  她迟早
knowing The Countess, it's just a matter of time
会割了我的喉咙
before she slits my throat.
何必等着别人
What's the point of waiting around for someone to...
背后给你一刀  死了不一了百了
stab you in the back when I'm already dead?
-不不不  -等等
- No, no, no, no, no. - Wait.
-让我做吧  -不
- Just let me do it. - No, no.
-我不想留在这儿了  -我知道
- I don't want to be here. - I know.
那你要永远困在这里了
Well, you're gonna be stuck here for all of eternity
除非你扣动扳机前
unless you get your head strapped on straight
什么都想清楚了
before pulling that trigger.
该死
Oh, shit.
天呐
Jesus.
你明白这回事的
You know how this goes.
嗯
Yeah.
我猜
And I'm guessing
你还有很多未了的心事吧
you have plenty of unfinished business still on your plate.
不  只有一桩
No, just one.
我儿子
My son.
我一直想弥补那事
I always meant to put that right.
告诉他很抱歉我抛弃了他
Tell him I'm sorry for leaving him.
好吧
Okay.
那你去做
So you do that.
这样我也有足够时间能取消《读者文摘》的订阅
And that'll give me enough time to cancel my Reader's Digest,
还有《乡村生活》
my Country Living.
然后我们就可以走了
Then we'll be ready to go.
我们
"We"?
你不用一个人来
You don't have to do this alone.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我以为你重生了
I thought you were reborn.
多诺万是我唯一的真爱
Donovan was my one true love.
他帮我从死亡边缘救回来时  我以为
I thought when he brought me back from the brink of death,
那是因为他爱我
it was because he loved me.
但他并不爱我
He doesn't love me.
他永远不会爱我
He never will.
那我们一起来
We'll do it together then.
利落地离世
Make a clean exit.
是的
Yes, dear,
科泰兹旅馆
the Hotel Cortez,
在洛杉矶市区
in downtown Los Angeles.
日子你也知道了
And you have the dates now.
是的
That's right, dear.
一周  你父亲请客
One whole week-- your papa's treat.
什么
What's that, um...?
他想问  "为什么是现在"
He wants to know, "Why now?"
我本想找到你父亲问问
Well, I'd hoped to reach your father to ask,
但找不到
but alas, I cannot.
我得走了  再见
I-I must away. Bye now.
真的
Really...
我的感想难以言表
I can't thank you enough.
如果你不介意我问
If you don't mind my asking,
你多久没见过他了
how long has it been?
我已经31年没见过我儿子了
I haven't seen my son in 31 years.
我写过信
I've written letters.
我一直有寄支票
God knows I've written checks.
而银行对账单总会告诉我支票都兑现了
The bank statement always let me know that each one cleared.
我把这当做
I took that as...
一种迹象
a sign.
我要提醒你
I must caution you.
你并不知道那年轻人是怎么想的
You don't know exactly the young man's aspect.
我不明白
I don't follow you.
他的世界观
His worldview.
你恐怕在要求他做到十分大度宽容
I-I fear you are challenging him to be very understanding.
你别说了
Let me stop you right there.
再我们那时候  同性恋知道不能生孩子
Back in my day, fairies knew never to father children.
那只会造成更多麻烦
It would, it would only add to the mayhem.
我亲戚  弗莱德里克
My cousin Frederick.
他总穿姐姐的
He was always getting into his sister's
女式睡衣和长袜
peignoir and stockings.
然后有一天  他找到了自己的位置
And-and then one day, he found his place.
他的人生坐标
His station in life.
在圣礼法衣中找到了宽慰
Took his comfort in the sacramental vestments.
他本可以当上大主教
He might've become a monsignor,
可惜他向自己的癖好屈服了
had he not succumbed to his appetites.
我不是个恋童癖
I'm not a pedophile!
我早就不关心
I lost interest long ago
你究竟自称是什么了
in whatever you claim to be.
不  我只知道  有个可怜的男孩
No, all I know is some poor boy
往后院丢球
threw a ball in the backyard,
突然
and suddenly
他骄傲的爸爸就不能接住那球了
his proud papa wasn't there to catch it.
而如今  这个男孩
So now here comes this same little boy
要来见个他一直想见的人
to visit someone he's always longed to see.
结果却见到了
And instead he's going to be confronted
蒂达·巴拉的鬼魂
by the ghost of Theda Bara.
这的确很吓人
I mean, it's-it's quite a fright indeed.
够了
That's enough!
总之
Anyhoo.
你答应给我的东西呢
Where's that item you promised me?
你没忘记你要做的吧
You haven't forgotten your end of the bargain.
请用
Have at it.
疯去吧
Go nuts.
谁能想到啊
Oh, who would have thought?
-肥皂里有氧气  -是啊
- Oxygen in the soap! - Yes.
老天爷  看啊
For God's sake, look.
"又白又亮"
"Radiant whites," It says.
你真是个奇迹
You are an absolute marvel.
就像圣诞节的早晨
It's like Christmas morning.
不可尊他神
耳朵
Ears.
他们聆听伪神的互换
For they heard the calling of false gods.
你是个聪明人  约翰·劳
You're a clever man, John Lowe.
放空你的心
Empty your hearts.
让影之女神听到你们的祷告
Let the Lady of Shadows hear your prayers.
欢迎来我们教会
Welcome to our church.
你是第一次来吗
Is this your first time here?
要知道旧神未死
Know that the old gods are not dead.
他们在等待唤醒
They're waiting to be awakened.
你叫什么
What is your name?
我是
I am...
死亡
death.
不
No!
再杀一个你就自由了
One more and you'll be free.
BGM: Lucretia My Reflection - Sister of Mercy
这是怎么回事
What is the meaning of this?
欢迎
Welcome.
多谢你来
Thank you for coming.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是谁
Who am I?
我是你  混蛋
I'm you, asshole.
我们得谈谈
We need to have a little talk.
我也不觉得你叫我来这儿
I didn't really think that you brought me here
是来翻你的旧衣服的
to rummage through your old clothes.
而且我反正对你不要的东西也不感兴趣
And I'm not interested in your castoffs anyway.
但我知道你喜欢我不要的
Though I know you're very interested in mine.
你了解我的生平吗
So, you know my entire biography?
在一堵墙后封了数十年
Damned behind a wall for decades.
如今要再次受罪
And now ready to be damned again.
我爱她
I love her!
你以为你爱他吗
You think you love him?
你爱的不过是一段远去的记忆
You love a distant memory.
你爱的是大银幕上的一个形象
You love an image on a screen.
你对他来说不过是个粉丝
You're nothing more than a fan to him.
你的怒气很常见
You know, your petulance is very common.
那些风光不再的帅气男孩
It is always this way with pretty boys
总会如此
who are past their prime.
你该长长胡子
You should grow out that little beard, you know?
或许你能在西部片里找到活儿干
Maybe you could find, uh, work in the Westerns.
我们不需要你
We don't need you.
你根本不知道
You know nothing
我有多聪明
of my resourcefulness,
小老鼠
little mouse.
你可以走了
You can go.
你在真实世界里
You wouldn't last two days
跟女伯爵连两天都撑不下去
with The Countess in the real world.
等她看到你听到交通直升机
Once she sees how you shit yourself
就吓得拉裤子  就会抛弃你
at the sound of a traffic helicopter.
我非常了解你
Oh, I know all about you.
我是史上最伟大的银幕情人
I am the greatest screen lover of all time.
你很廉价
You're cheap.
你一直很廉价
You've always been cheap.
你居然有把剑
You have a freaking sword.
我们第一次跳完探戈我就该杀了你
I should've killed you after our first tango.
死在这把剑下是你的荣幸
You should be honored to die by its blade.
得了
Bitch, please.
不是吧
Really?
现在谁是小老鼠了
Who's the little mouse now?
她会为这张帅气的脸痛苦的
She's gonna mourn over that pretty face.
你现在不漂亮了吧
You're not so pretty now, are you?
反正我的颧骨也比你好看
I have better cheekbones, anyway.
漂亮多了
Cheekbones for days.
救命  救命
Help! Help!
有人听得到吗  救命
Can anybody hear me?! Help!
随你怎么吼
You can scream as loud as you like.
事实上  那样更好
In fact, I prefer it.
你想要怎么样
What do you want from me?
救命  不要
Help me. No.
你失败了
You failed.
我是个承包商
I'm a contractor.
我会做乐观的估计
I make optimistic projections.
拜托  我愿做任何事
Please, I'll do anything.
我会弥补你的
I'll make this up to you.
求你  别这么做
Please, don't do this.
你叫我做什么都行  求你
I'll do anything you want, please.
求你  不要
Please don't.
守信  是一个人的基本品质
A man is only as good as his word.
你干什么
What are you doing?
保持练习
Keeping up the practice.
我为我们定下了宏大的计划
I have great plans for us, you and me.
自从我死后
Ever since my death,
我的狩猎场就受限了
my hunting grounds have been limited
只能在这间旅馆里
to the confines of this hotel.
这里虽然不错
And as rich as it may be,
但你可以拥有我只能
there are opportunities available to you
梦想的机会
that I can only dream of.
我老婆呢
Where's my wife?
别管她了
Forget her.
我觉得妻子只让人分心
I find spouses to be a distraction.
我怀疑我妻子就向警方检举了我
I suspect my own to have ended my career prematurely
害得我的事业过早结束
by turning me in to the police.
但我已经原谅她了
I've forgiven her, of course,
因为她是如此美丽
because of her immense beauty.
我得找到亚历克丝
I need to find Alex.
你知道她在哪
You know where she is.
当然
Of course.
我无所不知
I know everything.
我就只有时间和想象
I have nothing but time and imagination.
但我为我们做的打算  将超越十诫
But what I have planned for us, beyond the Ten Commandments,
将你提升至我们这行的巅峰位置
will elevate you to the zenith of our profession.
你可以获得这份荣誉  约翰
You take the glory, John.
我则谦卑地站在你的影子里
I'll stand humbly in your shadow.
告诉我她在哪
You tell me where she is
否则你的梦就只会是梦
or your dreams are just that.
早熟
Precocious.
我的明星学生当然会如此
I'd expect nothing less from my star pupil.
来吧
Come!
你的团聚等着你呢
Your reunion awaits.
新煮咖啡的蒸汽
There's nothing like the steam from a fresh pot
最能化肺部的痰了
to loosen the phlegm from the lungs.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们可别空着肚子争吵
You mustn't have an argument on an empty stomach.
那样一天都会不舒服
It upsets the balance of the day.
你叫醒我
I'm sure you didn't wake me up
肯定不是来喝咖啡的
to have a cup of coffee.
你告诉我霍尔登只是我的幻觉
You told me Holden was a hallucination.
那是谎言
That was a lie.
你想让我以为自己要疯了
You tried to make me think I was going crazy.
那是事实
Well, that was the truth.
你让我见不到自己的儿子
You kept my son away from me.
如果你还没注意到
In case you haven't noticed,
他已经不是你印象里的那个孩子了
he's not the child you knew.
我选择跟霍尔登在一起
I made my choice to be with Holden.
我没告诉你
I didn't tell you
是怕你会说什么改变我的主意
because I was afraid you would say something to change my mind.
我不后悔我的决定
I don't regret my decision.
我们还有一个孩子呢
We have another child.
我并没忘记斯嘉丽
I haven't forgotten about Scarlett.
这么久以来
All this time,
你只见过她两次
you've seen her twice.
她告诉我了
She told me.
你又去过外婆家几次
And how many times have you been to visit Grandma?
没有借口
No excuses.
我们抛弃了她
We abandoned her.
我们是世上最差的父母
We're the world's worst parents.
至少这事我们都同意
Well, at least that's one thing we can agree on.
或许没有我  斯嘉丽会过得更好
Maybe it'll be better for Scarlett with me gone.
那是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我们有麻烦了
We're in trouble.
我前一阵犯了个错误
I made a mistake a while ago,
女伯爵认为那是我的责任
and The Countess holds me responsible.
告诉我
Tell me.
一群野孩子
A pack of wild children
把人的血都吸光了
drained a man of all his blood.
你有什么想告诉我的吗  亚历克丝
Anything you want to tell me, Alex?
我救了我的病人  麦克斯得了麻疹要死了
I saved my patient. Max was dying from measles.
那你就转化了他  而他转化了其他人
So you turned him... and he turned the others.
给你一个机会解决这个问题
One chance to fix this problem.
女伯爵说她会杀了我和霍尔登
Countess told me she'd kill me and Holden
除非我解决问题
if I didn't make things right.
我知道这不是你的事
I know it's not your problem...
如果跟你和霍尔登有关
If it involves you and Holden,
那就是我的事
it's my problem.
我们怎么办
What do we have to do?
啪
Tap.
啪啪啪
Tap-tap-tap.
那是莫尔斯码的"他要上楼来了"
That's Morse Code for "He's coming up the stairs."
抓紧你的珍珠项链吧  爸爸
Clutch your pearls, Daddy.
老天爷
Good God.
没想到我会这么紧张
I didn't think I'd be so nervous.
你儿子已经在房里安顿好了
Your son is all settled in his room.
他知道有赠送的酒票
He knows about the complimentary drink tickets,
他来兑酒了
and here he comes to redeem them.
好了
Okay.
再见吧
Bye now.
下午好
Good afternoon.
现在是减价[快乐]时间
It's happy hour,
所以...
so...
想笑就笑吧
feel free to smile.
想不想
Maybe...
来点喝的
something to drink?
好
Sure.
波本威士忌加冰吧
How about a bourbon rocks?
再来杯苏打水
And a soda back, please.
我叫道格拉斯
I'm Douglas.
叫我丽兹就行
Call me Liz.
你是
What's your, uh...
你是做哪一行的
what's your line of work?
我为一个在丹佛附近
Uh, I work for a guy who owns huge properties packed
用自助仓库
with self-storage units
存放巨额财产的人工作
in and around Denver.
公司很能挣钱
Company makes some serious coin...
我可挣不了多少
not that I do.
顺便说一句  我喜欢你的裙子
Hey, I like your dress, by the way.
很耀眼
Sparkly!
你管它们叫什么
What do you call those?
什么
What?
那些圆东西
Uh, the... those round things.
这个
The... oh.
亮片
Paillettes.
然后...  我妻子
And then... then my wife insisted
坚持让我换工作
that I needed to find a new boss.
她说  倒不如
Or to... better yet, she said,
我自己当老板
to be my own.
我是说...
I mean...
别怪她
Give her a break.
你妻子可真精明
Your bride sounds astute.
是啊
Yeah.
确实
Yeah, she is.
可房贷一点都拖不了
But that doesn't make the mortgage payment any less late.
我们都有梦想  是吧
We all have dreams, you know?
但这不意味着就要抛弃一切
Not meant to drop everything...
不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
我不同意
I disagree.
你要继续奋斗
You go ahead.
搬去博尔德  成立你的皮艇公司
You move to Boulder and you start that kayak company.
抱歉  让你听我唠叨了这么久
Anyway, I'm sorry to bend your ear.
其实我一直不太健谈
I've always kept my own counsel, you know?
从小...
Coming up, it was, uh...
就只有我和妈妈相依为命
just my mom and I.
爸爸走了
Dad split.
错过了我打得最好的曲棍球联赛季
Missed my one great season in Pee Wee League.
我不能怪他
I can't blame the guy.
我当时是个淘气的孩子
I was a rambunctious kid.
这不怪你
You shouldn't blame yourself.
你父亲肯定有什么原因
I'm sure your father had his reasons.
我要是听说了原因
Well, those'll be news to me,
才新奇呢
whenever I hear 'em.
我心里一直想着他
I guess he's on my mind.
我来到这里是因为...
I'm in town 'cause we're...
我和爸爸终于联系上了
finally gonna reconnect.
为这干一杯吧
Here's to that.
好
Yeah.
下一杯我请
This, uh, next one's on me.
你真好
Nice of you.
还是下次吧
Maybe another time.
我很愿意
I'd like that.
我们来得太迟了
We're too late.
警察肯定已经追查到送货员了
The police must have tracked down the delivery boy.
孩子们一定早就不在了
Kids must be long gone.
也许没有
Maybe not.
里面有人
Somebody's inside.
待在这
Stay here.
你好
Hey there.
你叫什么
What's your name?
金米
Kimmy.
我要找妈妈
I want my mommy.
好  金米
Okay, Kimmy.
让我看看你怎么了
Let's see what's going on with you.
别碰她
Get away from her!
别动
Don't move!
你在流血
You're bleeding.
我没事
I'm okay.
别逼我开枪
Don't make me have to shoot you.
你吓不了我的
You don't scare me.
我们的人数比你们多多了
There's a lot more of us than you.
我们告诉过你别回来了
We told you not to come back.
金米
Kimmy!
求求你
Please.
求求你  你得帮帮她
Please, you have to help her!
玛蒂  后退
Maddie! Get back.
你准备好了吗  呼吸  准备好了吗
You ready? Breathe for me. Ready?
振作点  宝贝
Come on, honey.
振作点  金米
Come on, Kimmy.
-治好她  -我不能停
- Fix her! - I can't stop.
金米  醒过来
Kimmy, come on.
快醒来
Come here.
Come on.
你怎么停了
Why did you stop?
帮帮她
Help her!
对金米来说已经太晚了
It's too late for Kimmy.
醒醒啊
Come on.
对你们其他人来说还不晚
It doesn't have to be too late for the rest of you.
你丈夫失踪多久了  德雷克夫人
How long has your husband been missing, Mrs. Drake?
周三晚失踪的
Since Wednesday evening.
他跟我说的最后一句话是"我愿意"
Virtually the last thing he said to me was, "I do."
然后我来到这儿换衣服  收拾完东西
Then I came up here to change and finish packing.
他要去酒吧喝酒
He was going to the bar for a drink.
那是我最后一次听到他的消息
That's the last I heard from him.
换了是我还不至于惊慌  德雷克夫人
I wouldn't panic yet, Mrs. Drake.
有些新郎  他们会在婚礼后
Some grooms, um, they get cold feet
而不是婚礼前  打退堂鼓
after the ceremony instead of before.
你不了解我丈夫
Oh, you don't know my husband.
他是个非常负责的人
He's a very responsible human being.
他肯定不会就这样丢下新娘
He would never abandon his new bride
还有他年幼的儿子
or his young son this way.
肯定出了什么事
Something must have happened.
亲爱的  我不知道有客人来
Darling, I wasn't aware we had visitors.
我是威尔·德雷克
I'm Will Drake.
亲爱的
Dearest.
先生  你妻子以为你失踪了
Sir, your wife was under the impression you'd gone missing.
"失踪"
"Missing"?
不
No.
不  我刚在七楼看翻修的房间呢
No, I was just exploring the new renovation on the seventh floor
在走廊里迷路了两天
and got lost in the hallways for two days.
我很愿意带你一起看看
I'd love to show it to you.
-我妻子亲自设计的  -我们真不应该
- My wife designed it herself. - Oh, we couldn't possibly waste
你们真该看看里面都有什么
You really should see what's in there.
浪费警官们的时间
these officers' time any longer.
我太抱歉了
I am so sorry...
给你们添了这么多麻烦
for how I've inconvenienced you.
我糊涂了
I was... confused.
没事
Yeah.
我们很高兴  一切都好
Well, we're just glad everything turned out okay.
万事大吉  没有难看的局面发生
A happy ending without all the tugging and the pushing and...
谢谢  再次感谢你们
Thank you. Thank you again.
你杀了我  贱人
You murdered me, you bitch.
想开点吧
Oh, get over it.
是你先惹我的
You pissed me off.
你在侮辱巴塞洛缪
You made disparaging remarks about Bartholomew.
我忍不了
That I cannot abide.
胡扯
Bullshit.
你一直都是这么琢磨的
This was your plan all along.
那现在怎么办
So what happens now?
我的尸体出现在某条肮脏的小路上
My body turns up in some filthy alleyway?
你掌控我的帝国
You take control of my empire?
我会解散帝国  把它变成现金
I thought I'd dissolve the empire, convert it to cash.
你忘了
Well, you forget.
遗嘱里没有你
You're not in the will.
不  你忘了
No, you forget.
拉科伦继承一切
Lachlan inherits everything.
你让我成为了他的法定监护人
And you made me his legally appointed guardian.
我会监护他
I'll be guiding him.
直到他成年
Only until he reaches his majority.
假设他能活到成年
Assuming he ever does.
你拿我儿子威胁我吗
Are you threatening my son?
我不杀孩子  但我可以把他变成血亲
I don't kill children, but I could make him a blood relative.
你是说像那个在走廊里把我吸干的女人
You mean like that woman who sucked me dry in the hallway.
你死了之后比活着时聪明多了
You're a lot smarter dead than you ever were alive.
把这股聪明劲儿保持下去
Try and keep it that way.
何不去看看我们的儿子呢
Why don't you go visit our son?
我不想让他伤心
We wouldn't want anything to upset him.
告诉他我们最终决定不去巴黎度蜜月了
Tell him we decided not to honeymoon in Paris after all.
我建议过你不要在旅馆里杀他
I advised you not to kill him on the premises.
咬我啊
Bite me.
走廊尽头有间房
There's a room at the end of the hall.
都为你们准备好了
It's ready for you.
我会尽量给你们找些东西吃
I'm gonna try and find you something or someone to eat.
你们肯定饿极了
You must be starving.
我们可以在外面等你回来
We can wait out here till you get back.
我一会儿就回来
I'll just be a sec.
好吧
Okay.
来吧
Come on.
往里走
Go on in.
你朋友们等着你呢
Your friends are waiting for you.
我不想
I don't want to.
进去吧
Let's go.
-不  -不
- No! - No!
救命
Help!
开门  开门
Open up! Open it!
放我们出去  开门
Let us out! Open up!
麦克斯
Max!
跟你说了  不该相信那贱人
I told you, we should have never trusted that bitch!
闭嘴
Shut up!
妈妈
Mama...
闻到了美味
smells appetizers.
如果我像那群孩子一样
What if I look like teenager
被抓到了怎么办
that's about to get caught?
我们要离婚了
We're getting a divorce.
不该睡在一起
We're not supposed to be sleeping together.
谁说我们真要离婚了
Who says we have to go through with it?
我说的
I do.
我给你协议书后  有什么变化吗
Has anything really changed since I gave you the papers?
都变了
Everything.
你找到了霍尔登
You found Holden.
你也变了  对吧
You are different, aren't you?
你的眼神中多了一份坚定
Something solid behind your eyes.
你完全好了
You're all there.
你终于恢复了  约翰
Finally got it together, John.
我做不到
I can't.
我得慢慢来
I have to process this.
我还得看看霍尔登和孩子们
And I have to check on Holden and the kids.
但我很喜欢新的约翰
I am interested in this new John, though.
你射在她里面了
Did you come inside her,
还是像对我一样  射在她奶上了
or did you shoot on her tits like you do with me?
萨莉
Sally.
上妓女  就射在奶上
With the whore, it's always on the tits.
我对你来说就是吧
That's what I am to you.
妓女
A whore.
你错了
You're wrong.
不是这样的
It's not like that.
我说过你对于我的意义
I told you what you meant to me.
没错
Yeah.
你说过你爱我
You told me you loved me.
别想抵赖
And don't you dare deny it.
我不是骗子
I'm not a liar.
我爱过你
I have loved you.
但那只是上瘾般的着迷
But what we have is an addict's high.
当时看来永远不会散
In the moment, it seems like it's never ending.
但一切都有结束的时候
But it always ends.
不
Oh, no.
不  亲爱的
Oh, no, baby.
再也不会有我这样的人
There will never be anyone like me.
约翰
John...
你能说这不是你想要的吗
you can't tell me that this isn't what you want.
不
No.
亚历克丝不是你的归宿
Alex is not the answer.
她不了解你
She doesn't know about you.
没我了解你
Not the way I do.
她发现事实后要怎样么接受呢
How's she gonna take it when she finds out the truth?
你是个连环杀手
That you're a serial killer.
她会重新接受你吗
You think she'll take you back?
像我这样包容你
Accept you the way I do?
不  我得尽力一试
No, I have to try.
为了斯嘉丽和霍尔登
For Scarlett and for Holden.
鬼话
Bullshit.
这都是为了你自己
This is for you.
为了你
It's for you.
说得没错
You're right.
如果我要坦诚面对自己的话
If I'm being honest with myself.
她离开了你
She left you.
她骗了你
She lied to you.
她想把你赶出她的生活
She wanted you out of her life.
我陪了你五年
I was there for five years.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不该被这样对待
I deserve more than this!
滚开
Stay away from me.
你会回来的  混蛋
You'll be back, asshole!
她一旦知道你的真实面目  就会离开你
She'll leave you once she learns what you are.
她会离开你  不然我就去杀了那贱人
She'll leave you, or maybe I'll kill that bitch!
这是我见过
Oh, it's the most beautiful thing
最美的东西
I have ever laid eyes on.
谢谢你们  谢谢
Oh, thank you, thank you.
我...  要怎么用来着
Oh, oh, how-how... how do I use it again?
这个键摁一下是冷水
Uh, okay, you press this once for cold.
摁两下是热水
And twice for hot.
甚至单独设置了洗轻柔衣物的程序
And there's even a separate setting for delicates.
而且再也不用拧水了
Oh, and no more wringing.
再也不用拧水了
No more wringing.
美好的一天啊
Oh, heavenly day.
谢谢你帮我重新联系上我儿子
Thank you for helping me reconnect with my son
还帮他铺好床
and for giving him such excellent turndown service.
我们可以走了吗
So... good to go?
行  我看可以了
Oh, yeah, I think so.
我们定下办法了吗
Um, have we settled on a method?
药  枪  刀
Pills? Gun? Knife?
尼罗河女王  我得告诉你
Oh, Queen of the Nile, I must tell you.
你儿子在蓝鹦鹉酒吧坐了有一会儿了
Your son has been perched in the Blue Parrot for quite a while.
你想让我告诉他你不会去了吗
Would you like me to tell him that you will not be back?
-因为你要自杀  -该死
- Because you're doing yourself in? - Shit.
我想占用你一点时间
Mainly wanted a moment of your time.
行啊
Okay.
怎么了
Really?
我想跟你说些事情
I just wanted to tell you something.
珍妮丝和我要去博尔德了
Janice and I are Boulder-bound.
好啊  干一杯
Well, cheers to that.
谢谢你帮了一把
Thanks for the push in the right direction.
我也有事要告诉你
I have something to tell you.
这很难...  开口
And... it's... rather difficult.
爸爸
Hey... Dad.
其实不难
It's not difficult.
其实  不用你开口
Or... it doesn't have to be.
妈妈给了我一些线索
Mom gave me a few clues.
我梳理了一下
I put them together.
她警告我
She warned me
我会认不出你来  但我认出来了
that I wouldn't recognize you, but I-I did.
我认出来了
I mean, I do.
你身上没有我的影子
I don't recognize myself in you.
我怎么会这么幸运  养育出一个
How did I get so lucky to raise a child
如此
so...
善良的孩子
compassionate?
妈妈养育了我
Mom raised me.
你抛弃了我们
You left.
这很伤人
That hurt.
也许这也是为什么
And maybe that's what...
我能看清其他人一团糟的...
...makes me see when other people are all...
内心
messed up inside.
而且珍妮丝很懂我
Plus, Janice hears me, you know?
就算我连自己都不懂的时候
Even when I don't even know what I mean.
我告诉她
And I told her
我今晚要和你相认
that I was gonna make things good tonight.
她很为我俩高兴
And she's happy for us both.
你完全可以接受你父亲
You have no problem with the fact
是个女人的事实吗
that your father is a woman?
佩德罗在《真实世界》中死后
I really learned something when Pedro died...
我体会到很多
...on The Real World.
抱歉
Sorry.
我一直在感悟生活
And I kept learning.
说来话长了  丽兹
Plenty of time to talk it out, Liz.
但是
But, hey,
我的生活还有足够的空间去再多容纳一个女人
there's plenty of room for another woman in my life.
好的
Okay.
天啊  我太喜欢看你用刀了
My goodness, I do love watching you work with a knife.
接到你的电话我有点吃惊
I was a little surprised to get your call.
我还以为你会在巴黎
I figured you'd be in Paris,
谋杀亲夫呢
murdering your husband
然后把尸体扔进塞纳河
and dumping his body in the Seine.
我干了件蠢事
I did a rather stupid thing, I suppose.
但那会儿脑子一热
Felt great at the time,
现在得有一点小麻烦要处理了
but now I have a bit of a mess to deal with.
我知道你的意思
Oh, I know just what you mean.
我们出发度蜜月之前
Before we could leave for our honeymoon,
我们吵了一架
we had a squabble.
我把他和拉蒙娜关在了一起  她把他吃了
So I chucked him in with Ramona and she ate him.
亲爱的啊
Baby.
你自己独自欣赏了好戏
You hate-watched without me.
别生气
Don't be mad.
也许这周末的时候  我们可以扔点别的人进去
We can dump someone else in there, maybe this weekend.
与此同时  我需要帮我办点事
In the meantime, I need you to do something for me.
说吧
Name it.
我需要你
I need you
在威尔的尸体发臭之前
to retrieve Will's body
把尸体弄出来
before it gets too ripe.
我想拉蒙娜应该已经回铁笼子里去了
And I think Ramona should go back in the iron maiden.
没问题
Sure.
那我帮你擦屁股的时候
And while I'm cleaning up your mess,
你能否也帮我处理点麻烦
maybe you can clean up mine.
什么叫你的麻烦
What did you mean "your mess"?
何不发短信给你男朋友
Why don't you text your boyfriend
问问他呢
and ask him?
对了
Oh, oh, that's right.
他不知道怎么发短信
He doesn't know how to text.
视频聊天就更别想了
And you can forget about FaceTime.
门开着呢
It's open.
再等一下下
I just need a sec.
我不知道改选哪个
I wasn't sure what we-we landed on,
所以把选项都摆出来了
so I-I just put out a selection.
你随意挑吧
Help yourself.
天啊  你简直是个倒卖军火的
Christ, it's like you're an arms dealer.
好了
There.
天啊
God.
花的时间比我想的长多了
Ah, boy, it took a lot longer than I thought.
不过总算搞定了
But it's finally done.
什么东西
What is?
我的感谢视频
It's my tribute video.
我死了以后  没人会赞颂我的美德
Nobody's gonna be rushing to extol my virtues once I croak,
所以我决定给自己留点纪念
so I decided to immortalize myself.
给我点意见
Tell me what you think.
要说实话
And be honest.
我叫艾芮斯
听听我的呐喊吧
你是费了功夫的
You put a lot of work in this.
是啊
Yeah.
我希望我能给我的INS上三个粉丝
I just, I wanted it to be a beacon of hope
带去一丝希望的光
for my three followers on Instagram.
好了  我准备好了
Okay, I'm ready.
动手吧
Let's do this.
知道吗  我觉得
You know, I'm just thinking
黑猩猩那张照片应该放到彩虹前面
the chimp might go better before the rainbows.
放到"别丧失好奇之心"的后面
So it's over the "Never lose your sense of wonder" lyric.
你在拖延时间
You're stalling.
我的道格拉斯
My Douglas.
他说他希望我重回他的生活
He just told me he wants me in his life.
所以你不干了
So you're out.
如果哪天他有孩子了呢
What if one day he has kids?
我会是孩子的外婆  艾芮斯
I'd be a grandmother, Iris.
是啊  可我始终是孤零零的一个人
Yeah, well, I've lived alone all my life.
我爱过的每一个人都抛弃了我
Every single person I've ever loved has abandoned me,
你为什么就能不一样
so why should you be any different?
听我说  艾芮斯
Listen to me, Iris.
你和我
You and I
都是上了年纪的女人
are women of a certain age.
我们受过苦
We have suffered
都是不该受的罪
more than our fair share.
该死
Damn it.
我们才应该是这个世界的主人
We are the ones who should inherit the earth.
我们应该接管这个旅馆
We should freaking take over this damn hotel!
振兴这个地方
Spiffy it up.
让这里变成一个像你的彩虹视频一样
Turn it into a place with as much hope
充满希望的地方
as your rainbow montage.
就像《涉外大酒店》里的那样
Best Exotic Marigold Hotel.
我们被赋予了第二次机会
We're entitled to a second chance.
光荣
A glorious,
闪耀的谢幕
blazing final act.
我的
My...
朋友
friend...
最精彩的一幕还没开始呢
the best is yet to come.
这样一来就没有回头路可走了
If we do this, there's no going back.
爸爸
Daddy.
霍尔登
Holden.
Holden!
这一刻我已经不记得等了多少年了
I can't tell you how long I've waited to do this.
五年了
Five years.
他和我记忆中的一模一样
He's exactly how I remembered him.
他也会一直这样
And that's exactly how he'll stay.
该回家了
It's time to go home.
约翰
John!
她是谁
Who's that?
继续走
Just keep walking.
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you!
我发誓
I swear on my soul
我一定会杀了你
I'm going to kill you!
约翰
John...!
你没逃跑
You didn't run.
为什么要逃
Why would I run?
你一定会找到我
You'd only find me.
我找不到他了
I couldn't find him.
差不多得100年了
For almost a century.
我不知道他是死了
I didn't know if he was dead
还是抛弃了我
or had abandoned me.
但其实都不是
Neither of which were true,
因为至始至终  他就被困在这儿
because he'd been trapped here the whole time.
被困在这儿的不止是他
He's not the only one who's been trapped here.
我们都是
We all have.
至少现在他自由了
At least now he's free.
而且现在你知道了  他没有抛弃你
And this time you know he didn't abandon you.
这就是你想要的吗  多诺万
Is that what you want, Donovan?
所以你干下这样可怕的事
Is that why you did this terrible thing?
因为你想自由
Because you wish to be set free?
恐怕是的
I suppose I do.
我知道这意味着什么
I knew what this would mean.
我一看到他  就知道他意味着什么
I knew what he meant the moment I saw him.
他对你的意义
What he was to you.
是我永远做不到的
What I could never be.
他创造了我
He made me!
是他创造了我
He made me.
他造就了我的一切
He made me everything I am!
而你造就了我
And you made me
把我创造成他的样子
in his image.
是的
Yes, I did.
我努力把你变成他
I tried to.
我以为没有他  我会活不下去
I thought I couldn't be without him.
但你从来不是他
You were never him.
你永远成不了他
You could never be him.
所以你毁了他
So you destroyed him.
一找到机会我就这么干了
First chance I got.
你也知道我会回来杀你
And you knew I'd come back here to kill you.
是的
Yes.
而你毫不在乎
And you don't care.
我在乎
I do.
I do care.
我只是不介意死
I just don't mind.
死亡是你让我爱你的唯一办法
Dying is the only way you'll let me love you.
我想不出别的办法了
I don't know how else to do it.
美丽的少年啊
Beautiful boy.
愿意牺牲一切
Willing to sacrifice everything...
只为了我的爱
...for the love of me.
我竟创造了这样美丽的生灵
What a beautiful thing I've made.